Finding Aid for the Collection of Television Film Scripts PASC.0074
UCLA Library Special Collections
- DANIELLE STEEL'S FINE THINGS, (4/9/1990) (Box >138)
  Writers: Lefcourt, Peter
- DARK HOLIDAY, (1/31/1989) (Box >172)
- DARK MANSIONS, (2/10/1984) (Box > 87)
  Writers: McCullough, Robert L.
- DARK MIRROR, (10/6/1983) (Box >156)
- DARKNESS BEFORE DAWN, (5/18/1992) (Box >184)
- DATE RAPE, (3/11/1988) (Box > 31)
  Writers: MACDONALD, DONALD
- DAUGHTERS OF JOSHUA CABE (THE), (4/28/1972) (Box >111)
  Writers: Savage, Paul
- DAUGHTERS OF JOSHUA CABE RETURN (THE), (8/27/1974) (Box >121)
  Writers: Hite, Kathleen
- DAVID, (5/8/1987) (Box > 17)
- DAWN: PORTRAIT OF A TEENAGE RUNAWAY, (1/20/1976) (Box >143)
- DAY AFTER (THE), (5/7/1982) (Box >180)
- DAY AFTER (THE), (8/13/1982) (Box >167)
- DAY JFK DIED (THE), (4/28/1980) (Box >113)
  Writers: Phillips, Thomas Hal
- DAY OF RECKONING, (7/1/1996) (Box >215)
  Writers: Meyers, Chip; Straus, Bill
- DAY THE EARTH MOVED (THE) (FORMERLY: DEATHQUAKE), (5/17/1974) (Box >103)
  Writers: Turley, Jack; Zweiback, Martin
- DAY THEY TOOK THE BABIES AWAY, (1/26/1971) (Box > 39)
  Writers: Fischer, P.S.
- DEAD BEFORE DAWN, (6/4/1992) (Box >172)
  Writers: Ireland, John
- DEAD ON THE MONEY, (3/5/1990) (Box >127)
  Writers: Lambert, Gavin
- DEAD POET'S SOCIETY (TELEPLAY), (2/16/1990) (Box > 21)
  Writers: LaGravenese, Richard
- DEADLY HUNT (THE), (6/10/1971) (Box >167)
  Writers: Ludwig, Jerry; Bercovici, Eric
- DEADLY INTENTIONS (PARTS I AND II), (12/14/1984) (Box > 54)
  Writers: Marin, Andrew Peter
- DEADLY MATRIMONY (PARTS I & II), (5/7/1992) (Box >129)
  Writers: Laskos, Andrew
- DEADLY MESSAGES (FORMERLY: OUIJA), (10/23/1984) (Box >102)
  Writers: Bleich, Bill
- DEADLY SILENCE, A, (1/4/1989) (Box >179)
  Writers: Miller, Jennifer
- DEADLY SILENCE, A, (12/20/1988) (Box > 65)
- DEADLY TOWER (THE), (6/2/1975) (Box >179)
  Writers: Lansford, William; Hirsch, James G.
- DEADLY TOWER (THE), (11/22/1974) (Box >108)
  Writers: Lansford, William Douglas
- DEADMAN'S CURVE, (6/17/1977) (Box > 84)
- DEADMAN'S CURVE, (9/16/1977) (Box >198)
  Writers: Young,Dalene
- DEAR MR. GABLE, (no date) (Box > 40)
  Writers: Noxon, N.L.
- DEATH BE NOT PROUD, (10/7/1974) (Box > 26)
- DEATH BEFORE DISHONOR, (2/18/1984) (Box > 2)
- DEATH CRUISE, (8/6/1974) (Box >142)
- DEATH IN CALIFORNIA, A, (no date) (Box >158)
- DEATH OF A CENTERFOLD: THE DOROTHY STRATTEN STORY, (no date) (Box >122)
  Writers: Stewart, Donald
- DEATH OF INNOCENCE, A, (8/9/1971) (Box >119)
  Writers: Stefano, Joseph
- DEATH OF OCEAN VIEW PARK (THE) (FORMERLY: AMUSEMENT PARK), (4/22/1979) (Box >102)
  Writers: Oringer, Barry
- DEATH OF RICHIE (THE), (7/22/1976) (Box >162)
- DEATH ON THE FREEWAY, (10/18/1978) (Box > 99)
- DEATH ON THE FREEWAY, (12/5/1978) (Box >102)
- DEATH SENTENCE, (5/7/1974) (Box >105)
  Writers: Neufeld, John
- DEATH STALK, (no date) (Box >196)
  Writers: Kandel, Steven
- DEATH TAKES A HOLIDAY, (8/16/1971) (Box >201)
  Writers: Lakin, Rita
- DEATH TAKES A HOLIDAY, (7/8/1971) (Box >136)
- DECONSTRUCTING SARAH, (1/10/1994) (Box >204)
  Writers: Rose, Lee
- DECONSTRUCTING SARAH, (10/17/1993) (Box >204)
- DECORATION DAY, (1/29/1990) (Box >172)
- DEEP FAMILY SECRETS, (no date) (Box >219)
  Writers: Stettin, Monte; Madsen, David
- DEFECTION OF SIMAS KUDIRKA (THE), (4/22/1977) (Box >156)
  Writers: Feldman, Bruce; Stern, Sandor
- DEFIANT ONES (THE), (2/28/1985) (Box > 40)
  Writers: Barrett, J.L.
- DELANCEY STREET: THE CRISIS WITHIN, (10/9/1974) (Box > 60)
- DELIVER US FROM EVIL, (4/16/1973) (Box >133)
- DEMON MURDER CASE (THE), (10/12/1982) (Box >168)
- DEMPSEY, (1/19/1983) (Box > 2)
- DESCENDING ANGEL, (12/6/1989) (Box > 85)
  Writers: Woodard, Grace; Sharp, Alan and Siegel, Robert
- DESERT RATS, (3/6/1988) (Box > 65)
  Writers: Chisholm, David J.; Kowalski, Bernie
- DESPERADO, (8/7/1985) (Box >141)
  Writers: Leonard, Elmore
- DESPERADO: THE OUTLAW WARS, (12/9/1988) (Box >173)
  Writers: Wisher, William; Mirisch, Andrew
- DESPERATE LIVES, (4/10/1981) (Box >145)
  Writers: Hunter, Lew
- DESPERATE LIVES, (10/19/1981) (Box > 18)
- DESPERATE WOMEN, (10/17/1977) (Box > 84)
  Writers: Sowards, Jack
- DESPERATE WOMEN, (4/6/1978) (Box >186)
- DEVIL DOG: THE HOUND OF HELL, (4/28/1978) (Box >186)
  Writers: Karpf, Stephen; Karpf, Elinor
- DEVILS'S BED (THE), (7/26/1994) (Box >209)
- DIAMONDS (THE), (5/1/1993) (Box >209)
  Writers: Robinson, Todd
- DIARY OF A TEENAGE HITCHHIKER, (no date) (Box > 96)
  Writers: Young, Robert Malcolm
- DIARY OF A TEENAGE HITCHHIKER, (3/16/1979) (Box > 24)
- DINNER AT EIGHT, (6/30/1989) (Box > 76)
  Writers: Griffin, Tom; Marion, Frances
- DIRTY DOZEN III, (11/10/1986) (Box > 81)
  Writers: Rodgers, Mark
- DIRTY DOZEN IV: THE FATAL MISSION, (10/21/1987) (Box > 89)
- DIRTY DOZEN: THE NEXT MISSION, (8/22/1984) (Box > 40)
  Writers: Kane, M.
- DIRTY DOZEN: THE NEXT MISSION, (9/21/1984) (Box >136)
  Writers: Kane, Michael
- DISAPPEARANCE OF AIMEE (THE), (6/16/1976) (Box >166)
- DISAPPEARANCE OF FLIGHT 412 (THE), (6/24/1974) (Box >158)
  Writers: Simpson, George; Burger, Neal
- DISASTER AT SILO 7, (8/19/1988) (Box >186)
  Writers: McIntosh, Douglas
- DISASTER ON POTOMAC, (11/10/1983) (Box > 40)
  Writers: McGreevey, J.
- DISASTER ON THE COASTLINER, (7/17/1979) (Box > 92)
- DIVORCE WARS, (7/20/1981) (Box > 40)
  Writers: Wrye, D.
- DOCTOR STRANGE, (11/4/1977) (Box > 72)
  Writers: DeGuere, Philip; Lee, Stan
- DOCTOR'S PRIVATE LIVES, (1/20/1978) (Box > 40)
- DOCTOR'S STORY, A, (1/3/1983) (Box > 50)
- DOCTOR'S STORY, A, (6/26/1983) (Box > 81)
  Writers: Rubin, Ronald
- DOLLMAKER (THE), (no date) (Box >150)
  Writers: Cooper, Susan; Cronyn, Hume
- DOLLMAKER (THE), (no date) (Box > 40)
  Writers: Cooper, S.
- DON'T GO TO SLEEP, (7/1/1982) (Box >162)
  Writers: Wynn, Ned
- DON'T GO TO SLEEP, (no date) (Box > 77)
- DON'T JUST STAND THERE!, (2/8/1967) (Box > 72)
  Writers: Williams, Charles
- DON'T LOOK BACK: THE STORY OF SATCHEL PAIGE, (4/2/1979) (Box > 88)
- DOOMSDAY GUN, (10/30/1993) (Box >200)
  Writers: Bernstein, Walter
- DOWN THE LONG HILLS see LOUIS L'AMOUR'S DOWN THE LONG HILLS, (no date) (Box >)
- DR. COOK'S GARDEN, (7/30/1970) (Box >145)
  Writers: Wallace, Art
- DR. QUINN, MEDICINE WOMAN, (12/5/1991) (Box >205)
  Writers: Sullivan, Beth
- DRAW!, (10/4/1983) (Box >116)
  Writers: Mann, Stanley
- DREAM BREAKERS, (no date) (Box > 16)
- DREAM MAKERS (THE), (9/25/1974) (Box >108)
  Writers: Svanoe, Bill
- DREAM MERCHANTS (THE), (10/9/1979) (Box > 40)
  Writers: Krumholz, C.
- DREAM MERCHANTS (THE) (PART II), (7/6/1979) (Box > 41)
- DREAM STREET, (6/10/1987) (Box > 81)
  Writers: Rosner, Mark
- DREAM WEST (PARTS I, II, III), (12/14/1984) (Box > 27)
- DRESS GRAY, (3/6/1981) (Box > 2)
- DRESS GRAY, (1/18/1980) (Box > 90)
  Writers: Vidal, Gore
- DRIVE, (9/29/1995) (Box >249)
  Writers: Phillips, Scott
- DROP-OUT FATHER, (12/21/1981) (Box >196)
  Writers: Shanks, Bob
- DUMMY, (10/19/1978) (Box > 41)
  Writers: Tidyman, E.
- DUMMY, (7/13/1978) (Box > 41)
- DYING TO BE PERFECT, (3/15/1996) (Box >218)
  Writers: Smith, Susan Arnout
- EARLY FROST, AN, (7/19/1985) (Box > 35)
  Writers: Cowen, R.
- EARLY FROST, AN, (5/20/1985) (Box >191)
  Writers: Cowen, Ron; Lipman, Daniel
- EARLY FROST, AN, (6/26/1985) (Box > 41)
- EARTH ANGEL, (8/31/1990) (Box >127)
  Writers: Shengold, Nina
- EAST OF EDEN (PART III), (1/1/1981) (Box > 88)
  Writers: Shapiro, Richard A.; Steinbeck, John
- EICHMANN IN MY HANDS (Released as The Man Who Captured Eichmann), (10/16/1995) (Box >256)
  Writers: Chetwynd, Lionel; Harwood, Ronald
- EIGHT IS ENOUGH: NOT JUST ANOTHER WEDDING, (7/10/1989) (Box > 83)
  Writers: Strangis, Greg
- ELEANOR AND FRANKLIN, (10/16/1973) (Box >144)
  Writers: Costigan, James
- ELEANOR AND FRANKLIN, (6/26/1975) (Box >122)
- ELEANOR AND FRANKLIN (THE) WHITE HOUSE YEARS, (9/7/1976) (Box >189)
- ELEANOR, FIRST LADY OF THE WORLD, (11/9/1981) (Box > 95)
  Writers: Ladner, Caryl; Mandelbert, Cynthia
- ELENA, (10/30/1984) (Box > 31)
  Writers: Baum, Thomas; Stern, Sandor
- ELEVATOR (THE), (no date) (Box > 96)
  Writers: Ketchum, David; DiMarco, Tony
- ELLERY QUEEN, (12/6/1974) (Box >117)
- ELLIS ISLAND (PART 1), (3/19/1984) (Box >188)
  Writers: Stewart, Fred Mustard; Newman, Christopher
- ELLIS ISLAND (PART 2), (3/19/1984) (Box >188)
- ELLIS ISLAND (PART 3), (3/19/1984) (Box >188)
- ELVIS, (10/16/1978) (Box >139)
  Writers: Lawrence, Anthony
- ELVIS, (no date) (Box > 42)
  Writers: Lawrence, A.
- ELVIS AND THE BEAUTY QUEEN, (12/8/1980) (Box >167)
  Writers: Cameron, Julia
- EMBASSY (BY MCGREEVEY, J.), (11/9/1984) (Box > 47)
- EMBASSY (BY YOUNG, D.), (4/25/1984) (Box > 25)
- EMERGENCY ROOM, (6/26/1982) (Box > 6)
- EMERGENCY ROOM, (8/10/1982) (Box >161)
  Writers: Viola, Joe A.
- EMMY AWARDS (39th Annual Special), (no date) (Box >221)
  Writers: Leverence, John
- EMPEROR'S NEW CLOTHES (THE), (1/18/1984) (Box >205)
  Writers: Curtiss, Mark; Ash, Rod
- ENEMY WITHIN (THE), (7/6/1993) (Box >209)
  Writers: Bass, Ronald; Ponicsan, Darryl
- ENOLA GAY, (no date) (Box > 99)
- ER, (2/24/1994) (Box >199)
  Writers: Crichton, Michael
- ESCAPE, (7/3/1970) (Box > 93)
  Writers: Playdon, Paul
- ESCAPE, (3/14/1979) (Box > 98)
  Writers: Zagor, Michael
- ESCAPE, (no date) (Box > 6)
  Writers: Binder, J.
- ESCAPE (THE), (11/17/1994) (Box >245)
  Writers: Busby, Scott
- ESCAPE FROM BOGEN COUNTY, (4/11/1977) (Box > 79)
- ESCAPE FROM TERROR: THE TERESA STAMPER STORY, (8/8/1994) (Box >241)
  Writers: Carr, Camilla; Klenhard, Walter
- EVENING IN BYZANTIUM, (5/1/1978) (Box > 42)
  Writers: Larson, G.
- EVENING OF COUNTRY GREATS (2nd Annual Special), (no date) (Box >225)
- EVERY MAN NEEDS ONE, (7/12/1972) (Box >112)
  Writers: Kleinschmitt, Carl
- EVERY MAN NEEDS ONE, (7/12/1972) (Box >250)
- EVERYBODY DOES IT (SPECIAL), (1/27/1984) (Box >243)
  Writers: Cooper, Paul W.
- EVERYBODY'S BABY: THE RESCUE OF JESSICA MCCLURE, (2/15/1989) (Box > 32)
  Writers: EYRE, JR., DAVID
- EVIL ROY SLADE, (10/21/1971) (Box >197)
  Writers: Belson, Jerry; Marshall, Garry
- EVITA (Released as Evita Peron), (no date) (Box >255)
  Writers: Harwood, Ronald
- EXECUTION (THE), (7/6/1984) (Box >116)
- EXECUTIONER'S SONG (THE), (4/15/1981) (Box > 42)
  Writers: Mailer, N.
- EYE FOR EYE, (3/20/1958) (Box > 68)
- FACE OF A STRANGER, (no date) (Box >126)
  Writers: Norman, Marsha
- FACE OF FEAR (THE), (7/15/1971) (Box >139)
- FACE OF FEAR (THE), (1/8/1990) (Box >185)
  Writers: Glueckman, Alan Jay; Koontz, Dean R.
- FACE OF RAGE (THE), (12/23/1982) (Box >161)
  Writers: Sitowitz, Hal; Wrye, Donald
- FAILING OF RAYMOND (THE), (1/12/1971) (Box >202)
  Writers: Spies, Adrian
- FALL FROM GRACE, (1/2/1990) (Box > 95)
  Writers: Trevey, Ken
- FALLEN ANGEL, (6/10/1980) (Box > 42)
  Writers: Hunter, L.
- FALLEN ANGEL, (no date) (Box > 3)
  Writers: Cummins, Jack; Pugsley, Don
- FALLING FOR YOU, (no date) (Box >213)
  Writers: Kring, Timothy
- FAMILY KOVAC (THE), (12/16/1973) (Box >122)
- FAMILY OF ONE, A, (2/19/1982) (Box > 42)
  Writers: Lewin, R.
- FAMILY OF SPIES (PART I), (12/21/1988) (Box > 57)
  Writers: Adams, Richard Delong
- FAMILY OF SPIES (PART I), (9/30/1988) (Box > 74)
- FAMILY OF SPIES (PART II), (10/3/1988) (Box > 57)
- FAMILY REUNION: A RELATIVE NIGHTMARE, (8/15/1994) (Box >208)
  Writers: Clifton, Patrick J.
- FAMILY RICO (THE), (6/12/1972) (Box >119)
  Writers: Karp, David
- FAMILY SECRETS, (6/23/1983) (Box >241)
  Writers: Thuna, Leonora; Powers, Stefanie
- FAMILY SECRETS, (1/1/1982) (Box > 68)
- FAMILY UPSIDE DOWN, A, (9/29/1977) (Box >146)
- FANTASIES, (6/18/1981) (Box >107)
- FAST FRIENDS, (5/5/1978) (Box > 68)
- FATAL VISION, (no date) (Box > 43)
- FATHER AND SON, (5/20/1991) (Box >248)
- FATHER FIGURE, (1/24/1980) (Box >153)
- FATHER'S HOMECOMING, A, (2/22/1988) (Box >206)
  Writers: Katz, Gloria; Huyck, Willard
- FAVORITE SON, (2/16/1988) (Box > 14)
  Writers: Sohmer, Steve
- FAVORITE SON, (1/19/1988) (Box > 14)
- FDR'S LAST YEAR, (no date) (Box > 14)
- FEAR ON TRIAL, (3/17/1975) (Box >171)
  Writers: Rintels, David W.; Faulk, John Henry
- FEMALE ARTILLERY, (11/24/1972) (Box >133)
  Writers: Freeman, Bud
- FEMINIST AND THE FUZZ (THE), (9/14/1970) (Box >100)
  Writers: Henerson, James
- FEVER, (no date) (Box >125)
  Writers: Brothers, Larry
- FIGHT FOR LIFE, (7/10/1986) (Box > 8)
- FIGHTER (THE), (6/27/1982) (Box >147)
  Writers: Kass, Jerome
- FIGHTING BACK, (3/13/1980) (Box > 99)
  Writers: McNeely, Jerry
- FIGHTING CHOICE, A, (8/22/1985) (Box > 59)
  Writers: Buck, Craig
- FIGHTING FOR MY DAUGHTER: ANNE DION STORY, (4/22/1994) (Box >215)
  Writers: Blakeney, ERic
- FILTHY RICH, (no date) (Box >215)
  Writers: Olson, Alfa-Betty; Efron, Marshall
- FINAL DAYS, (1/12/1989) (Box >182)
  Writers: Whitemore, Hugh
- FINAL DAYS, (11/1/1988) (Box >182)
- FINAL JEOPARDY (THE), (8/9/1985) (Box >174)
  Writers: Hendryx, Shirl; Hochberg, Victoria
- FINAL VERDICTS, (4/4/1990) (Box > 86)
  Writers: Roman, Lawrence; Rogers St. Johns, Adela
- FINISH LINE (THE), (no date) (Box > 84)
  Writers: Franklin, Rose
- FINISH LINE (THE), (1/11/1989) (Box > 15)
- FINNEGAN BEGIN AGAIN, (2/12/1981) (Box > 43)
- FINNIGAN BEGIN AGAIN, (1/7/1981) (Box > 43)
  Writers: Lockwood, W.
- FIRE, (no date) (Box > 47)
- FIRE AND RAIN, (2/1/1989) (Box > 74)
  Writers: Sherman, Gary; Chandler, Jerome Greer
- FIRE IN THE SKY, (10/13/1977) (Box > 86)
  Writers: Gallico, Paul; Nemec, D.; Balluck, D.; Blankfort, M.
- FIRE ON THE MOUNTAIN, (6/11/1980) (Box > 70)
- FIRE ON THE MOUNTAIN, (4/10/1981) (Box > 19)
- FIRE! TRAPPED ON THE 37TH FLOOR, (3/25/1990) (Box >126)
  Writers: Bloom, Jeffrey
- FIREHOUSE, (no date) (Box >210)
  Writers: Cucci, Frank
- FIRST AFFAIR, (4/20/1983) (Box >179)
- FIRST GENTLEMAN (THE) (SPECIAL), (1/28/1994) (Box >245)
  Writers: Palm, Robert
- FIRST LADIES (THE) (Special), (no date) (Box >227)
- FIRST MODERN OLYMPICS (THE) 1896 (PART I), (6/22/1983) (Box > 69)
  Writers: Bast, William; Allison, Charles Gary
- FIRST MODERN OLYMPICS (THE) 1896 (PART II), (6/22/1983) (Box > 69)
  Writers: Bast, William
- FIRST STEPS, (3/15/1984) (Box >190)
  Writers: Browning, Rod
- FIRST YOU CRY, (1/23/1978) (Box > 70)
- FITZGERALDS AND THE KENNEDYS (THE), (6/28/1988) (Box > 32)
  Writers: HANLEY, WILLIAM
- FIVE DESPARATE WOMAN, (6/10/1971) (Box > 43)
  Writers: Norman, M.
- FIXING THE SHADOW, (4/1/1990) (Box >206)
- FLASH, (no date) (Box >254)
  Writers: Merrick, Monte
- FLATBED ANNIE AND SWEETIEPIE: LADY TRUCKERS, (9/21/1978) (Box >160)
  Writers: Robinson, Robie
- FLESH AND BLOOD, (4/26/1982) (Box > 8)
  Writers: Johnson, Monica
- FLIGHT 90: DISASTER ON THE POTOMAC, (11/10/1983) (Box > 43)
- FLIGHT TO HOLOCAUST, (9/22/1976) (Box >120)
  Writers: Heverly, Robert
- FLOOD, (7/9/1976) (Box >166)
  Writers: Ingalls, Don
- FLORENCE NIGHTINGALE, (8/10/1984) (Box >147)
  Writers: Moffat, Ivan; Goldemberg, Rose Leiman
- FLORIDA STRAIGHTS, (no date) (Box > 4)
- FLY AWAY HOME, (no date) (Box >142)
  Writers: Siliphant, Stirling
- FLYING HIGH, (2/14/1978) (Box > 89)
  Writers: Cohan, Marty; Aldredge, Dawn
- FOR LADIES ONLY, (3/23/1981) (Box > 44)
  Writers: Riley, J.
- FOR LOVE OR MONEY, (3/18/1983) (Box > 93)
  Writers: Henerson, Jim
- FOR LOVE OR MONEY, (11/20/1984) (Box > 9)
- FOR LOVERS ONLY, (5/21/1982) (Box >182)
  Writers: Hirsch, James G.
- FOR THEIR OWN GOOD, (6/16/1991) (Box >184)
  Writers: Kaplan, Ed
- FOR US (THE) LIVING, (10/4/1982) (Box >241)
  Writers: Davis, Ossie
- FORBIDDEN LOVE, (12/29/1991) (Box >142)
  Writers: Leggett, Laurian
- FORGOTTEN (THE), (12/8/1988) (Box > 73)
  Writers: Keach, James; Railsback, Steve
- FORGOTTEN MAN (THE), (1/11/1971) (Box >116)
- FORGOTTEN MAN (THE), (12/22/1970) (Box >133)
- FOSTER AND LAURIE, (3/25/1975) (Box >170)
  Writers: Ruben, Albert; Silverman, Al
- FOUL-UPS, BLEEPS AND BLUNDERS (Shows 201-204), (no date) (Box >223)
- FOUND MONEY, (9/6/1979) (Box >113)
  Writers: Fairman, Michael; Sanders, Richard
- FRANCIS GARY POWERS: THE TRUE STORY OF THE U-2 SPY INCIDENT, (2/11/1976) (Box >166)
- FRANK NITTY: THE ENFORCER, (9/18/1987) (Box >185)
  Writers: Zlotoff, Lee David
- FRAUD BROADS, (3/16/1984) (Box > 27)
  Writers: Dial, Bill; Chapman, Richard
- FREEDOM ROAD, (9/5/1978) (Box > 24)
  Writers: Goodman, David Zelag
- FRENCH ATLANTIC AFFAIR (THE) (PART I), (4/4/1979) (Box > 96)
- FRENCH ATLANTIC AFFAIR (THE) (PART III), (5/14/1979) (Box > 98)
- FRENCH ATLANTIC AFFAIR (THE) (Parts I,II,III), (6/26/1979) (Box > 4)
- FRESNO (PARTS I, II, AND III), (3/12/1986) (Box > 80)
  Writers: Kemp, Barry
- FRESNO (PARTS IV AND V), (3/12/1986) (Box > 80)
  Writers: Petryni, Michael
- FRESNO (PARTS I-V), (6/11/1986) (Box >179)
- FRIENDLY FIRE, (7/25/1978) (Box >115)
  Writers: Kanin, Fay
- FRIENDLY PERSUASION, (10/28/1974) (Box > 3)
  Writers: Wood, William; West, Jessamyn
- FRIENDS TIL THE END, (9/27/1996) (Box >219)
  Writers: Opotowsky, Anne; Rowell, Kathleen
- FRIENDS/MY GIRLFRIEND IS BACK, (10/19/1984) (Box > 59)
  Writers: Marsh, Linda; Peters, Margie
- FROM HEAVEN WITH LOVE (SPECIAL), (3/8/1982) (Box >199)
  Writers: Harmon, Bruce
- FROM HERE TO ETERNITY, (1/3/1978) (Box > 44)
  Writers: McGuire, D.
- FROM HERE TO ETERNITY, (2/17/1978) (Box > 44)
- FROM HERE TO ETERNITY, (6/19/1978) (Box > 44)
  Writers: Gast, H.
- FROM HERE TO ETERNITY (WAR YEARS/PEARL HARBOR), (6/19/1979) (Box > 44)
- FRONT PAGE (THE) (SPECIAL), (no date) (Box >243)
  Writers: Hecht, Ben; MacArthur, Charles
- FUGITIVE FAMILY, (4/10/1979) (Box >100)
- FUN & GAMES, (11/23/1979) (Box > 44)
  Writers: Smilow, D.
- GAMES MOTHER NEVER TAUGHT YOU, (2/24/1982) (Box >159)
  Writers: Coe, Liz
- GANG IN BLUE, (10/3/1995) (Box >245)
  Writers: Natkin, Rick; Fuller, David
- GATHERING (THE), (2/1/1977) (Box >171)
  Writers: Poe, James
- GATHERING (THE) (PART II), (9/4/1979) (Box > 93)
  Writers: Longstreet, Renee; Longstreet, Harry
- GATHERING (THE) (PART II), (9/19/1979) (Box >171)
- GENERATION, (10/3/1984) (Box >242)
- GEORGE WASHINGTON (PART III), (7/22/1982) (Box > 45)
  Writers: Fielder, Richard
- GEORGE WASHINGTON (PARTS I, II, III), (6/2/1983) (Box > 45)
  Writers: Fiedler, R.
- GETTING PHYSICAL, (7/28/1983) (Box > 9)
- GETTYSBURG, (11/12/1993) (Box >202)
  Writers: Waters, Krystal
- GHOST OF A CHANCE, (no date) (Box > 30)
  Writers: Bradford, Hank
- GIDEON'S TRUMPET, (no date) (Box >100)
  Writers: Rintels, David W.
- GIDEON'S TRUMPET (STEP OUTLINE), (no date) (Box >)
  Writers: Maltz, Albert
- GIFT (THE), (2/5/1979) (Box >135)
  Writers: Hamill, Pete
- GIFT OF LOVE (THE), (9/1/1978) (Box >154)
  Writers: Ledner, Caryl
- GIMME THAT GOOD TIME ROCK 'N' ROLL (Special), (no date) (Box >234)
  Writers: Elbling, Peter; Leo, Malcolm
- GIRL ON THE LATE, LATE SHOW (THE), (1/21/1974) (Box >143)
- GIRLS OF THE WHITE ORCHID, (3/24/1983) (Box >153)
  Writers: Raschella, Carole; Raschella, Michael
- GLADIATOR (THE), (10/22/1985) (Box >128)
- GLITZ, (2/1/1988) (Box > 66)
  Writers: Zito, Stephen
- GLITZ, (2/2/1988) (Box >204)
- GO ASK ALICE, (9/26/1972) (Box >151)
- GO WEST, YOUNG GIRL, (1/26/1978) (Box > 79)
  Writers: Yanok, George
- GODCHILD (THE), (9/16/1973) (Box >108)
  Writers: Bishop, Ron
- GOLDEN GLOBE AWARDS (42nd Annual Special), (no date) (Box >223)
- GOLDEN MOMENT (THE): AN OLYMPIC LOVE STORY (PART I), (12/19/1979) (Box > 98)
  Writers: Peckinpah, David E.
- GOLDIE AND THE BOXER, (2/13/1979) (Box > 4)
- GOLDIE/BOXER GO TO HOLLYWOOD, (11/10/1980) (Box > 45)
  Writers: Brez, M.
- GOLIATH AWAITS, (2/12/1981) (Box > 78)
  Writers: Bluel, Richard; Fiedler, Pat
- GOLIATH AWAITS, (1/6/1981) (Box > 45)
  Writers: Bluel, R.
- GOOD FIGHT (THE), (7/13/1983) (Box >247)
  Writers: Gutcheon, Beth
- GOOD SPORT, A, (3/17/1983) (Box > 78)
  Writers: Margolin, Arnold
- GOODBYE, MISS 4TH OF JULY, (11/12/1987) (Box > 65)
  Writers: McCormick, Kathy
- GOODNIGHT, MY LOVE, (3/27/1972) (Box >174)
  Writers: Hyams, Peter
- GOODNIGHT, MY LOVE, (5/16/1972) (Box >118)
- GOTTI, KIND OF THE VOLCANO, (11/28/1994) (Box >240)
  Writers: Shagan, Steve
- GRACE KELLY STORY (THE), (10/9/1982) (Box >187)
  Writers: Mandelberg, Cynthia
- GRACE KELLY STORY (THE), (6/30/1982) (Box > 77)
- GRAMBLING'S WHITE TIGER, (3/21/1981) (Box > 97)
  Writers: Potter, Lou; Attaway, William
- GRAMMY AWARDS (27th Annual Special), (no date) (Box >229)
- GRAMMY AWARDS (29th Annual Special), (no date) (Box >235)
- GRAMMY AWARDS (37th Annual Special), (2/21/1995) (Box >226)
- GRAND ISLE, (5/1/1990) (Box >127)
  Writers: Chopin, Kate; Anderson, Hesper
- GRAND VIEW, (no date) (Box > 4)
- GRASS IS ALWAYS GREENER OVER THE SEPTIC TANK (THE), (4/20/1978) (Box >176)
  Writers: Clair, Dick; McMahon, Jenna
- GREAT AMERICAN BEAUTY CONTEST (THE), (12/6/1972) (Box >112)
- GREAT CASH GIVEAWAY GETAWAY (THE), (10/10/1977) (Box >109)
  Writers: Reisman Jr., Phil
- GREAT ESCAPE (THE) (PART I: THE HUNTED), (9/3/1986) (Box > 70)
  Writers: Davis, Walter Halsey; Brickell, Paul
- GREAT ESCAPE (THE) (PART II: THE HUNTER), (9/22/1986) (Box > 70)
- GREAT HOUDINIS (THE), (5/17/1976) (Box >163)
  Writers: Shavelson, Melville
- GREAT ICE RIP-OFF (THE), (5/10/1974) (Box >105)
  Writers: Minoff, Lee
- GREAT PRETENDER (THE), (11/30/1989) (Box >127)
  Writers: Cannell, Stephen J.; Monterastelli, Art
- GREAT SANTINI (THE), (8/11/1982) (Box > 45)
  Writers: Raucher, H.
- GRIDLOCK, (no date) (Box > 31)
  Writers: Hern, Avie
- GRIFF, (2/20/1973) (Box >201)
  Writers: Cohen, Larry; Tokatyan, Leon
- GRIFFIN AND PHOENIX, (8/4/1975) (Box >101)
  Writers: Hill, John
- GUARDIAN (THE), (no date) (Box > 92)
- GUESS WHO'S SLEEPING IN MY BED?, (no date) (Box >109)
  Writers: Chais, Pamela Herbert
- GUILTY CONSCIENCE, (10/11/1984) (Box >189)
- GULAG, (3/13/1984) (Box >112)
  Writers: Gordon, Dan
- GULLIVER'S TRAVELS (FILM TWO), (4/10/1995) (Box >220)
  Writers: Moore, Simon
- GUN AND THE PULPIT (THE), (12/13/1973) (Box >170)
  Writers: Bowers, William
- GUN IN THE HOUSE, A, (9/17/1980) (Box >121)
  Writers: Zito, Stephen; Miller, James M.
- GUS BROWN AND MIDNIGHT BREWSTER, (3/8/1984) (Box > 81)
  Writers: Mitchlll, Scoey
- HANDS OF A STRANGER (PARTS I, II), (no date) (Box > 82)
  Writers: Daley, Robert; Kopit, Arthur
- HANGING BY A THREAD!, (no date) (Box > 46)
  Writers: Spies, A.; Allen, Irwin
- HAPPY, (1/27/1983) (Box > 5)
  Writers: Williams, Larry B.
- HAPPY, (4/25/1983) (Box >157)
  Writers: Williams, Larry B.; Rapoport, I.C.
- HAPPY, (no date) (Box > 5)
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY, BOB (Special), (no date) (Box >222)
- HAPPY ENDINGS, (no date) (Box > 76)
  Writers: Canaan, Christopher
- HARD COUNTRY, (10/29/1979) (Box > 4)
- HARDBALL, (2/27/1989) (Box > 32)
  Writers: NORTON, BILL L.
- HARDBALL, (12/8/1988) (Box > 32)
  Writers: PALM, ROBERT
- HARDHAT AND LEGS, (no date) (Box > 5)
- HARDHAT AND LEGS, (no date) (Box >249)
  Writers: Gordon, Ruth; Kanin, Garson
- HAUNTED (THE), (11/13/1990) (Box >173)
  Writers: Cloud, Darrah
- HAUNTED TRAILER (THE) (SPECIAL), (12/9/1976) (Box >243)
  Writers: Specht, Robert
- HAUNTING PASSION (THE), (3/25/1983) (Box >168)
- HAUNTS OF THE VERY RICH, (3/20/1972) (Box >112)
- HAVE YOU TRIED TALKING TO PATTY (SPECIAL), (10/9/1984) (Box >199)
  Writers: Gansberg, Alan L; Gansberg, Judith M
- HAVE YOU TRIED TALKING TO PATTY? (SPECIAL), (9/27/1985) (Box >243)
  Writers: Gansberg, Alan; Gansberg, Judith
- HAYWIRE (PARTS I, II), (2/14/1979) (Box > 46)
  Writers: Davis, P.
- HEADS, (no date) (Box >207)
  Writers: Stapelton, Jay
- HEAR NO EVIL, (6/9/1982) (Box > 69)
- HEAR NO EVIL, (6/21/1982) (Box >159)
- HEART OF A CHAMPION: THE RAY MANCINI STORY, (1/25/1985) (Box >175)
  Writers: Nemec, Dennis
- HEART OF DARKNESS, (12/13/1993) (Box >199)
  Writers: Christiansen, Bob; Rosenberg, Rick
- HEARTSOUNDS, (7/2/1982) (Box >249)
- HEARTSOUNDS, (2/20/1984) (Box >188)
- HEARTSOUNDS, (7/2/1982) (Box > 46)
- HEIDI, (9/18/1967) (Box >252)
  Writers: Hamner, Earl
- HEIST (THE), (5/10/1972) (Box >101)
  Writers: Siegel, Lionel E.
- HELL HATH NO FURY, (10/19/1990) (Box >126)
  Writers: Bensink, Beau
- HELL TOWN, (no date) (Box >118)
- HELP WANTED: MALE, (12/1/1980) (Box > 18)
  Writers: Shulman, Max
- HELP WANTED: MALE, (9/25/1981) (Box > 31)